Remove  deformed bars and move REINFORCEMENT Bar  in the place of Deformed Bars
Remove  structural steel sections completely 
1.Mild Steel Bars 10 mm
 
Mild Steel Round Bar û 10mm 
Specification:
Mild Steel Square Bar, available in various  sizes 6 to 32 mm  diameterBottom of Form
2) Reinforcement bar
 Reinforcement Bar 8 mm
Specification:
Reinforcement Round bar  available in various  sizes 6 to 32 mm  diameterBottom of Form
3) Flat bars 
Flat bars 10x 3 mm size
Specification:
Flat  bar  available in various  sizes 10 x 3,13X3 mm,13 X 5 mm, 13 X 6 mm,16x5 mm etc
4) Serrated Bar
  Serrated bar 20 mm x 3 mm
Specification:
Serrated bar available various sizes 3mm to 5 mm at various depths of 20mm to 70mm.
Remove  Timber instead add white wood  & remove Hardwood 1) White Wood 2) Plywood 3) Moisture Resistance MDF 4)  Solid Core Chip Board
White Wood  Canadian White Wood  WXW50
Canadian White Wood  WXW50
Specification
Size
1'' x 2'', 1'' x 4'', 1'' x 6'', 2'' x 2'', 2'' x 3'', 2'' x 4'', 2'' x 12'', 3'' x 3'', 4'' x 4''
2) Plywood 
Ply Wood û Hardwood 
Various type ply wood available û Bendy Plywood, Birch Plywood, Commercial plywood, Film faced plywood, Veneer plywood  WBP plywood
Moisture Resistance MDF 
Specification MR MDF No soggy sagas, only style! Secret weapon: water-repelling glue, maybe a waxy dip. Pulped, pressed, prepped, ready to conquer damp.
Solid Core Chip Board
                   áSolid Core Chip Board 38 mm thickness .size 915 x 2135mm
Solid Core Chipboard is easy to work with and can be finished with laminates, veneers, or paint, providing a versatile solution for various design
Aluminum Sectionds
Aluminium 40 x 20 x 1.2 mm Rectangular Hollow 5.95M
Specification: hape Form
Hollow
Shape Profile
Rectangular hollow profile, Rectangular Hollow Section (RHS)
Cross Section Dimensions
0.2 CMT (height)
Length
5.95M
Thickness
Uniform wall thickness
Width
5 CMT
 GI PIPES
Strong, tough and corrosion-resistant
Popular choice in various applications for aesthetic appearances
Available sizes range from 20NB to 100NB
Thickness range from 1.2mm to 2.5mm
Copper Pipes
Copper Pipe/Tube 1/4"-6" Inch Diameter x 1' foot Length
Metal Sheets
0.8mm Thick Metal Plate 1050 Grade Aluminium Sheets
1) keep interior paints 2) exterior paints  3) Industrial Coating 4)  Primers
Interior paint
Jotun Fenomastic My Home Smooth Silk Base A (900 ml)
Brand:Jotun
Exterior Paint
Weathercoat Anti Dustt TT
Brand:BERGER
100% acrylic emulsion exterior wall paint
Unique Dust Guard technology.á
3)Industrial Paint   
Jotun Penguard Topcoat
Brand : JOTUN
This is a 2 Component Product (A + B), 
Both are Included  5L Consists of 4 + 1 Litre 
 4)primers
National Paints PVA Primer White
Brand :National Paints
Color :White 
Itme Type : PVA Primer
Keep only
1)Waterproofing Materials
2)Adhesives &Sealants
Remove ( Cement, sand and aggregates & Cement Masonry ) 
Water Proofing Materials 
SIKALITE 
 Ready To Use Powdered Waterproofing 
Admixture For Cement/Sand Mortars and Concrete
2)Adhesives &Sealants
SIKA - Universal Multipurpose Silicone Sealant 
For Glazing And Weatherproofing - Sikasil-116 Gp White
    
Keep only first two items  
1) Fiber Cement Board
2) Gypsum Board
Remove (Particle board, Cement fibre Board , Regular Gypsum )  use the same pictures for first two option.                                                 
Fiber Cement Board
ideal for cladding, partition walls, ceilings, and facades.
Gypsum Board
Standard Gypsum dimensions (1200 x 2400 x 12mm - 15mm) 
 user-friendly installation features.
 Hammers    
Fibre Glass nail Hammer  450 Gramms
Brand : Stanley
Wrenches   
Combination Wrench Set
Combination wrench 10 mm
Combination wrench 12 mm
Combination Wrench 14 mm
Brand : Stanley
 
Spirit Levels  
Spirit Level 12" Professional 
Brand :UKEN
     
Measuring Tape
Stanley Measuring Tape 8M Bimaterial
8-meter length, suitable for large-scale measurements.
Bimaterial build for added comfort and durability.
Clear, accurate markings for precise results.
Ideal for construction, carpentry, and industrial use.
Robust Stanley design ensures long-lasting performance.
 
 
Safety Equipment
Safety Shoe  
        Model #á50053-127-44
                 Brand :DEWALT
PLANE Low Cut Safety Shoes - Size 39-44, Steel Toe, Taupe Suede, SB Rated, Oil Resistant
Combination Pliers
Use same image 
Dynagrip Combination Plier 180MM
Forged carbon steel jaws and handle providesá long life
Heat treated to ensure durability and optimal performance
For greater reliability, induction hardened at cutting edges,
Induction hardened for high performance, Ergonomically designed
Stanley Tools set û REMOVE THE ITEM û NOT REQUIRED
 
Backhoe Loaders 
JCB 4CX Super Backhoe Loader
The primary design features of the 4CX-14 SUPER backhoe loader are the four equal-sized tires which provide high ground clearance and traction, and 4-wheel steer capability for enhanced manoeuvrability. Additionally, a host of performance, comfort, safety and efficiency enhancements enable this machine to tackle loading operations like no other.
Compact Loader ( delete option 4 )
 
Remove 3rd & 4 th one ( DELETE Tractor Units & Ashok Leyland Truck)
Industrial Mixer
Imer Multi-Mix 350 Mortar/Concrete Mixer w/Steel Drum
Brand : IMER
Drum Capacity :12 Cu ft
Motor Power 1.9 hp
 
